<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hriman Shah</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hriman Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social And Behavioral Factors Affecting COVID-19 Transmissibility</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Title and Introduction The main purpose of this project is to evaluate the impact of social and behavioral factors on COVID-19 transmissibility. In order to accomplish this, we looked at various population statistics, health statistics, dietary factors, COVID-19 positive cases, and COVID-19 tests administered in different countries around the world in the year 2020. The first dataset describing different health indicators, such as access to hand washing facilities and sanitation services, along with general population data, such as the urban and rural population percentage, unemployment percentage, and the percentage of the population above the age of 65 were obtained from the ‘Health Nutrition and Population Statistics’ dataset on the World Bank website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social And Behavioral Factors Affecting COVID-19 Transmissibility (Project 2)</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Title and Introduction The main purpose of this project is to evaluate the impact of social and behavioral factors on COVID-19 transmissibility. In order to accomplish this, we looked at the ‘covid2020’ dataset which is a merged dataset composed of the ‘countryhealthstats’ dataset from the World Bank website, ‘diet2020’ dataset from Kaggle, and ‘totaltests’ dataset from the ‘Our World in Data’ website. The variables contained in the ‘covid2020’ dataset are the % of urban population, the % of unemployment, the % of rural population, the % of people above the age of 65, the % of people with access to proper sanitation, alcohol intake as a percentage of total calories in diet, the % of obesity, the % of population with confirmed covid cases, the % of population dead due to COVID-19, the population, and the total yearly tests for different countries around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
